onefootball.com 2015-04-28

# Onefootball - Privacy policy

### As of November 2014

Onefootball GmbH (hereinafter “Onefootball”) takes protecting users’ data privacy very seriously. The collection and use of your personal data occurs solely within the parameters of the applicable data protection law’s legal provisions. With this privacy policy statement, Onefootball provides information about the nature, scope and purpose of the collection and use of personal data. This privacy policy can be accessed here on this website at any time and applies to all online offers, content, features and services within this website. For our Apps we have a separate privacy policy statement, which you can read [here](http://www.onefootball.com/app-privacy-policy-en.html) or directly in the Apps. 

### 1\. Responsible authority 

The responsible authority according to the Federal Data Protection Act (hereinafter “BDSG”) is:   

Onefootball GmbH   
Greifswalder Str. 212  
D-10405 Berlin   

If you have any suggestions or questions about data privacy, please contact Onefootball via the email address [feedback@onefootball.com](mailto:feedback@onefootball.com). 

### 2\. Collection and use of data

Onefootball collects personal data only insofar as you voluntarily provide it and to the extent that such collection is permitted by law or agreed to by written consent.   
Personal data encompasses any information concerning the personal or factual information about a specified or specifiable natural person in accordance with § 3 (1) of the BDSG. This includes information such as name, physical address, e-mail address, telephone number, and, if applicable, user data.   
When accessing the Onefootball website, your Internet browser automatically transmits data for technical reasons. The following data is stored separately from other data that you submit to us: 

  * date and time of access,
  * browser type/version,
  * operating system used,
  * URL of the previously visited web page,
  * amount of sent data.

This data is stored exclusively for technical reasons and will not be allocated at any time to a specific person. 

### 3\. Newsletter

Onefootball provides a free newsletter service. The newsletter will inform you about new products or events and send you general information about the Onefootball Apps. By entering your e-mail address you can receive the newsletter. You can unsubscribe at any time with immediate effect via the link in each newsletter or on our website. 

### 4\. Disclosure of data 

As a general principle, Onefootball does not give your personal information to third parties. To the extent permitted by law, Onefootball may authorize other companies to perform various tasks, such as promotional support or technical services for the apps. These external service providers may have access to personal data to the extent necessary to perform the respective tasks. This data is used only to fulfill the particular task and not for any other purpose. Onefootball reserves the right to use or disclose information to the extent necessary to comply with laws, regulations or legal requirements, in particular to protect the integrity of the website and to support law enforcement agencies and investigations concerning public security. 

### 5\. Cookies & counting method

5.1 Statistical data is collected when users access the Onefootball website; however, this data is not associated with your person. This data collection serves to improve our website and to provide you as the user with the most extensive functionality possible.   
We use web beacons in this app, which can be explained as a simple programming code that lets us know when the website has been displayed or clicked on. To this end, Onefootball uses certified products, in particular Google Analytics. You can find more detailed information you on <http://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy>. By using this website, you agree to the third-party processing of data for the purpose outlined above. 

5.2 Cookies are small files that a website transferrs to the hard disk of the person using the Internet browser for the purposes of data collection. Through cookies, the website can store important data and your user experience can be tailored to fit your preferences. Like most websites, Onefootball uses cookies to improve your online experience and to offer a wide range of features. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies automatically. If you do not want to use of cookies, you can prevent cookies from being stored on your computer by adjusting the settings of your Internet browser. Note that the functionality and scope of our website may be restricted. 

### 6\. Links

Onefootball may provide links to other websites that are operated by companies other than Onefootball. If you click a link on our website and thereby choose to visit another website, please note that the respective privacy policies of that website operator apply. Onefootball is not responsible for the privacy policies of other companies. 

### 7\. Deletion, access to and correction of data 

We delete your data insofar as it is no longer required for the aforementioned purposes. If data must be retained for legal reasons, it will be locked. The data is then no longer available for further use. You can receive information at any time about the personal data we have stored about you. To do so, send us an e-mail at [feedback@onefootball.com](mailto:feedback@onefootball.com). 

### 8\. Counting method

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy. The current version is always available here.
